你住的小屋在哪
So, where's your place?
穿过树林一英里吧
About a mile through the woods.
大农村
This is rustic.
你的后院很大啊
Some backyard you got here.
我喜欢这里的安静
Yeah, I like the quiet.
我讨厌死安静了
Ugh, I fucking hate it.
怎么  你脑海中有太多声音吗
What, too many voices in your head?
你无法想象
You have no idea.
你应该找人聊聊
You should talk to someone about that.
你以为我为什么载你一程
Why the hell do you think I gave you a ride?
你真是诚实
Well, you're just so honest.
我诚实  你安静
I'm honest. You're silent.
我们都有自己的问题
We both got our things.
真正让你受伤的是什么
So what's your real damage?
显然你是在为什么事惩罚自己
I mean, you're obviously punishing yourself for something.
我们都有后悔的事  对吧
Hey, we've all got shit we wish we hadn't done, right?
那你后悔的事是什么
And what shit do you wish you hadn't done?
酒喝得还没那么多  我们还没到无话不谈的地步
Oh, we definitely haven't drank enough for all that.
这时候你要告诉我
So is this the part where you tell me
原谅自己  继续向前了吗
to just forgive myself and move on?
我不知道你做过什么
I don't know what you did.
可能你做的事不可原谅
Maybe it's not forgivable.
你原谅自己了吗
Did you forgive yourself?
没有
No.
但我也不会因此惩罚自己
But I don't punish myself either.
反正我知道
I mean, I figure the world's gonna
这个世界会惩罚我的
do that to me one way or another anyway.
你想谈谈丽贝卡·鲍曼吗
You want to talk about Rebecca Bowman?
-我不是说...  -不要说了
- I'm not judging-- - Don't.
-迟早...  -我说不要说了
- Sooner or later-- - I said don't.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我只想弄明白
I'm just trying to figure out
这案子上  我会不会一直碰到你
if I'm gonna keep running into you on this.
我们都知道  我无法阻止你到处调查
We both know I can't stop you from poking around,
但如果你有事别瞒着我
but it would make my life easier
那我的日子会好过很多
if you could just keep me in the loop.
当然
Of course.
谢谢你载我一程
Thanks for the ride.
别这么客气
Don't be a stranger.
听着  我这几天真的很不好过
Listen, I've had a really bad few days.
我们不是说好了吗
I thought we had a deal.
你不能碰丽贝卡
Rebecca was off-limits to you.
你一直知道我住这里
You knew I was living here?
我以为你在保护她
I thought you were keeping her safe.
那不是我的责任
That wasn't my responsibility.
上她是你的责任吗
Fucking her was?
我应该现在就杀了你
I should kill you right now.
那你就快动手吧
Well, get the fuck on with it.
你给我找到杀她的人
You find whoever did this to her.
联调局会负责
FBI has it covered.
联调局会逮捕他  很可能杀了他
FBI is gonna arrest him, most likely kill him.
但你要把他带给我
You bring him to me.
你需要找个其它地方住了
And you'll need to find another place to live.
黑吃黑
第四季
第五集
一个月前
动手吧
Let's go.
鲍曼女士  我真的认为应该...
Ms. Bowman, I really think we should--
把保险箱给我拿出来
Take out the goddamn box.
菲利克斯
Felix...
我的钱呢
Where's my money?
-鲍曼女士  -我的钱他妈去哪儿了
- Ms. Bowman-- - Where the fuck is my money?!
你舅舅
Your uncle.
他来拿走了
He came and took it.
什么
What?
那是我的保险箱  你不能...
That's my box. You can't just...
你们有规定的
There are rules.
丽贝卡  把枪收起来
Rebecca, put that gun away.
把枪收起来
Put that gun away.
没事  菲利克斯
It's okay, Felix.
-给我们两分钟时间  -好的
- Just give us two minutes. - Yes.
你疯了吗
Have you lost your mind?
你拿走了我的钱
You took my money?
从我的脱衣舞俱乐部偷拿现金
Skimming cash from my strip club,
然后锁在一个保险箱里  并不能让钱变成你的
locking it in a box doesn't make it yours.
虽然你可能没有把钱当工资给我
You may not have paid me that money,
但那是我应得的
but I earned it.
每一分都是
Every fucking penny.
如果你想拿枪指着我
If you want to point that at me,
那最好准备好开枪了
you had better be ready to shoot it.
开枪啊
Shoot it!
之后我会再和你谈
We'll talk about this later.
瓦茨  别闹了  这是胡闹
Watts, come on, man. This is bullshit.
你给我闭嘴  让你做什么就做什么
You shut the fuck up and do as you're told.
美好的早晨啊  是不是
Beautiful morning, isn't it?
让我想起重获自由是多么幸运
Reminds me of how blessed I am to be a free man.
你说有东西给我看
You said you had something you wanted to show me.
没错
That I do.
这边请  先生们
Right this way, gentlemen.
我女婿彻底搞砸了
My son-in-law's epic fuckup
可能让你有了不正确的看法
may have given you the unfortunate and grossly inaccurate idea
认为兄弟会无法
that the Brotherhood might not be able
满足你的需求
to deliver the muscle you need.
但现在我来了  我想让你亲眼看看
But I'm here now and I wanted to show you firsthand
我以后一定严格管理
I'll be running a much tighter ship.
你的工厂被烧那晚  是庞尼·乔负责的
Pony Joe here was in charge the night your factory got torched.
-瓦茨  -动手
- Watts... - Do it.
马上
Now.
拜托
Come on.
不要
No.
你知道那不是我的错
You know it wasn't my fault!
加尔文
Calvin!
不要这么对我
Hey, don't you do this!
不要
Don't do this!
求你
Come on!
加尔文  加尔文
Calvin! Calvin!
不要  加尔文
Don't do this! Calvin!
动手  加尔文
Let's go, Calvin.
-开车  伙计  -不要
- Hit it, boy! - Don't do this.
我对搞砸事情绝对零容忍
I will have zero tolerance for fuckups.
-生产拖延的事怎么办  -已经开始准备了
- What about the production delays? - Already started outfitting--
八天内我要三吨货
I need three tons in eight days.
要这么多买家肯定是南美人
That kind of volume usually means beaners.
这会在两国边境
Attract a lot of unfriendly attention
吸引很多不友好的注意
on both sides of the borders.
不得不承认  你还真是有胆量
You got one hell of a pair of balls on you, I'll give you that.
事成后女妖镇会成为
Banshee will become the distribution hub
整个东海岸的分销中心
for the entire East Coast pipeline.
只要你靠得住
As long as I can count on you,
兄弟会肯定会拿到丰厚的酬劳
the Brotherhood will be well compensated.
雇我是没问题
Employed is fine and good,
但现在你说的是贩毒集团
but you're talking about the cartels now.
要冒这种风险
And for that kind of risk,
我不想拿酬劳
I don't want to be compensated.
我想分一杯羹
I want a piece.
瓦茨先生
Mr. Watts,
你要能按时送货
you make this delivery on time,
我保证我们会就你的那一份达成协议
I'm sure you and I will come to an agreement about your piece.
很好
Glad to hear it.
听到了吗  小领结
You hear that, bow tie?
我们要成为哥们儿了
You and me is gonna be buddies.
好了
Well...
比预想的还顺利
that went better than expected.
我们刚为那个德国佬杀了一个自己人
We just killed one of our own for that fucking Dutchie.
不是他就是你
Yeah, it was him or you.
你不要以为我没考虑过
Don't think I didn't consider it.
快去清理干净吧
Now go clean this shit up.
恭喜  贾伯
Congratulations, Job.
28小时
28 hours.
这是新纪录
That's a new record.
虽然你跟警卫的较量
Now, your over-under with the guards
结果不太好  但是
wasn't too good, but...
我从未怀疑过你
I never doubted you.
为什么
Why?
你为什么不干脆杀了我
Why ain't you just killed me yet?
可以啊
I could do that.
我可以
I could.
但说实话
But honestly,
那样我会想念这些小环节的
I'd miss these little sessions of ours.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
这是下来的一个方法
That's one way to get down.
做得好  贾伯
Well played, Job.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
I'm fine.
又做恶梦了吗
More nightmares?
-如果你想谈谈...  -不想
- If you ever want to talk about it-- - No.
好吧
Okay.
你还是可以帮上忙的
You can still make yourself useful.
这是什么鬼东西
What the fuck is this?
你今天要做的家务列表
That is a list of your chores for the day.
天下没有免费午餐
No free lunches.
简直胡扯  我正在疗养恢复
This is bullshit. I'm convalescing.
我要去镇上一趟  一会儿见
I'm going into town. I'll see you later.
我不擦窗户
I do not do windows!
他们放你出来了
So they let you out.
对  你好像很惊讶
Yeah, you sound surprised.
没有
No.
你身上出了什么事我都不惊讶
Nothing surprises me anymore when it comes to you.
但无论如何
But for what it's worth,
我很肯定  你没有杀那个姑娘
I was pretty sure you didn't kill the girl.
非常感谢
Thanks very much.
拜托
I mean, come on.
你有多了解过一个人
How well do you ever know a man?
贾伯怎么样
How's Job?
你怎么不自己去
Why don't you pay him a visit
亲自看看他的情况
and find out for yourself?
我会的
I will.
你浑身一股烟味
You smell like an ashtray.
我那边失火了
Yeah, I had a fire.
普罗科特干的
Proctor.
是啊  他因为
Yeah, he was pretty angry
你跟他外甥女的事很生气
about your relations with his niece.
那样还是不能说明我是杀人犯
That still doesn't make me a murderer.
也不能说明他是
Doesn't make him one either...
尤其是这个案子里
in this particular case.
我可以去旁边房间洗个澡吗
You mind I go next door, take a shower?
你只能用我房间的了
You have to use mine.
你的房间里全是白蚁
Your place belongs to the termites.
灭虫人员说我们只能把房子烧了
Exterminators say we got to burn the place down
才能消灭它们
else they'll be over here.
那样倒也最好
That's probably for the best, huh?
你有地方住吗
You got a place to stay?
你应该离开
You should go.
这不是个好主意
This is a bad idea.
你觉得我们是在做自己吗
You think we are who we are?
还是你觉得我们可以改变
Or you think we can change?
你是说像你这样的人吗
What, you mean people like you?
女性十码靴印
跟我说说你父亲
Tell me about your father.
有必要吗
Seriously?
我知道是陈词滥调
I know it's a cliche,
但我认为我们都同意在你的治疗上
but I think in this case we can both agree
你父亲是很有影响的
your father was influential.
从何说起呢
What's there to tell?
我父亲是禽兽  罪有应得
My father was a monster that got what he deserved.
你真的这么认为吗
Do you really believe that?
有一晚我梦到他了
I had a dream about him the other night.
我们在康尼岛的木板路上
We were at Coney Island at the boardwalk.
那时我还是小女孩  夏天的时候
He used to take me there every Sunday
每到周日  他就会带我去那里
in the summertime when I was a little girl.
骑车之后我们会吃爆米花和咸味太妃糖
After the rides, we would have popcorn and saltwater taffy.
我们会一起坐在长椅上
And we would sit on the same bench
他会给我讲我妈妈的故事
and he would tell me stories about my mother.
然后我们把鞋脱掉把脚放在海浪里
Then we'd take our shoes off and put our feet in the surf.
梦里发生了什么
And what happened in the dream?
什么都没有
Nothing.
我也不知道
I mean, I don't know.
我们只是在那里
We were just there.
你想他了
You miss him.
这得多操蛋
How fucked up is that?
快看这是谁又被放出来了
Well, look who got out of jail again.
你还好吗
So how you doing?
你看起来好多了
You look better.
是啊  我依然打扮时髦
Yeah, I'm a real fashion plate.
你呢
How about you?
我怎么了
What about me?
我听说我不在的时候你入乡随俗了
I hear you went native while I was away.
是啊  可以这么说吧
Yeah. That's one way of putting it.
还有别的说法吗
You got another way?
听着  贾伯  我试着找过你
Listen, Job, I tried to find you.
我们都是
We all did.
道尔顿死了以后
After Dalton was dead--
是你杀了他吧
You mean after you killed him.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
我是那样认为的
I believed it.
我内心深处的
And then something--
某个东西
something inside me, it just--
我放弃了
I gave up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
本可能更糟
Well, it could have been worse.
有可能要十五年呢
Could have been 15 years.
不是你害了我
You never put that shit on me.
兔子坑了我们
Rabbit fucked us.
对  是他
Yes, he did.
在我眼皮底下
On my watch.
宝贝  那些操蛋事
Baby, all our bullshit...
都已经过去了
that's all in the past.
你和我
You and me,
我们都不能让时光倒流
we ain't ever getting that time back.
所以
So...
你现在真正需要担心的
what you really need to worry about
是当前眼下在发生的事情
is what's happening in the here and now.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我们的小朋友正在建一座碉堡
Our little friend is building a fortress
她武装到了牙齿
and she is armed to the teeth.
为了什么
For what?
看起来她觉得纪念她逝去丈夫的唯一方式
Seems she feels the only way to honor her dead husband
就是自己打完和普罗科特的战争
is to finish his war on Proctor herself.
瓦茨先生计划让五条生产线全部运行
Mr. Watts has made provisions to
保证出货供给
keep all five facilities running around the clock.
我需要你盯着
I'll need you to keep an eye on things.
我不信任他
I don't trust him.
如果我不能兑现对哥伦比亚人的承诺
If I don't deliver on my promise to the Colombians,
会有比瓦茨更棘手的麻烦
Watts is gonna be the least of our problems.
停车
Stop the car. Stop the car.
抱歉打扰  市长先生
Excuse me, Mr. Mayor?
是你扣押着丽贝卡·鲍曼的尸体吗
Mrsis withholding Rebecca Bowman's body?
你他妈在干嘛  米里亚姆
What the hell are you doing, Miriam?
我们想要回她  凯  你不能这样扣着她
We want her back, Kai. You can't keep her like this.
-我没有扣着她  -你可以弥补的
- I'm not keeping her. - You can fix it.
丽贝卡不是唯一被杀害的姑娘
Rebecca wasn't the only girl who was killed.
我们只需要埋葬她
She's the only one we need to bury.
这样扣着她的尸体是不对的  是不敬
It's not right keeping her body like this. It's disrespectful.
我给你两分钟让这些人离开
I'm gonna give you two minutes to get these men out of here.
没有丽贝卡的尸体我们是不会走的
We will not leave without Rebecca.
当你们驱逐丽贝卡的时候已经失去了对她的权利
You lost all rights to Rebecca when you shunned her.
如果你们现在不离开的话
If you don't leave right now,
我会把你们都拽走关进监狱
I'm gonna have you dragged away and put into jail.
我们再也不怕你了  凯
We are not scared of you anymore, Kai.
你对我们束手无策
There's nothing else you can do to us.
我可不这么认为
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
-市长先生  -市长先生
- Mr. Mayor? - Mr. Mayor?
-普罗科特市长  -普罗科特市长
- Mayor Proctor... - Mayor Proctor...
回家去吧
你们所有人
马上滚
否则你们都得进监狱
滚
先生
Sir, sir.
我们应该进去
We should go inside.
马上让这些人消失  明白吗
I want these steps cleared right now. You understand?
-他们有许可  -我不在乎
- They have a permit. - I don't give a shit.
女妖镇警察局
天呐  胡德
Jesus Christ, Hood.
下午好  警长
Afternoon, Sheriff.
你知道你刚才违反了多少条法律吗
You have any idea how many laws you just broke?
你要再逮捕我一次吗
You gonna arrest me again?
如果你是来让我道歉的  那没戏了
If you came looking for an apology, you're not gonna get one.
不  换我也会那么做的
No. I would have done the same thing.
-换你估计会一枪打死我  -可能吧
- You would have shot me. - Yeah, maybe.
你想怎样
What do you want?
听说又有一个姑娘遇害了
Heard there was another girl.
对  20岁的大学生
Yeah, 20-year-old college student.
有线索吗
Any leads?
只有一个基本不会说英语的
Other than a six-year-old witness
六岁目击者  除此之外没了
who can barely speak English, no.
什么都没有
Nothing.
你是不会置身事外的  对吧
You're not gonna stay out of this, are you?
我必须要问
You know, I got to ask,
你真不知道她怀孕了吗
you really didn't know she was pregnant?
不知道
No.
那一定很震惊吧
Must have been quite a shock.
节哀  胡德
I'm sorry, Hood.
-弗兰西斯小姐  -对
- Miss Francis? - Yes.
我是女妖镇警察局的布罗克·洛特斯警长
I'm Sheriff Brock Lotus from the BSD.
找到您妹妹尸体后我们谈过话
We spoke after your sister was found.
我记得  我已经回答过全部问题了
I remember. I already answered all your question.
-还有联调局的  -我知道
- The FBI, too. - No, I know.
我们很感激
And I-- we appreciate it.
这是吉尔的私人物品
These are Jill's personal belongings.
我只是来把它交给你
I just want to return them to you.
我能想象您现在有多痛苦
Look, I can only imagine how hard this must be for you.
那个人杀了三个女人却还逍遥法外
This guy killed three women and he was still out there free
最后害死了吉尔
walkng around to kill Jill?
你可是警长啊
I mean, you're the sheriff.
保护她是你的职责
It was your job to protect her.
我知道
I know.
玛吉来电
你好啊  柯特
Howdy, Kurt.
-你出来了  -他们放了我
- You're out. - They let me go.
于是我开始琢磨
And it got me thinking.
谁都应该有重新来过的机会
Everybody deserves a second chance.
回来吧  柯特
Come back to the family, Kurt.
我们需要你
We need you.
现在更需要
Now more than ever.
加尔文只会夸夸其谈
Calvin, he talks a big game,
但他终归没有你我的本事
but he ain't made of the same steel you and I are.
你想让我回归兄弟会
You want me to rejoin the Brotherhood?
有了对女妖镇警署的了解
With your knowledge of BSD procedure,
你会比从前更有价值的
you'd be more valuable than before.
来吧
Come on.
你觉得呢
What do you say?
兰道尔
Randall...
我不知道你是怎么出来的
I don't know how you got out.
但你来这里是个错误
You made a mistake coming back here.
此话怎讲
How's that?
因为既然我知道你出来了
Because now that I know that you're out,
我一定尽我所能把你关回去
I'm gonna dedicate myself to putting you back in.
是啊
Yeah.
我没预料到你会直接来咬我
I didn't expect you to bite right away.
还是老样子  对吧
I mean, hell, you got to be you, right?
今晚我要欢度良宵
Well, look, tonight I'm gonna party.
庆祝我重获自由
Celebrate my emancipation.
但明天我就会开始工作
Tomorrow I'm gonna get to work.
届时如果你还没接受我的邀请
If you haven't accepted my offer by then,
那我就第一个处理你
you're gonna be the first order of business.
海伦  把大家都叫来
Helen, call everybody
告诉他们一小时后举办新闻发布会
and tell them I'm holding a press conference in one hour.
你要做什么
What are you gonna do?
做我之前就该做的事
What I should have done a while ago.
这是什么意思
What is the meaning of this?
你不能再在女妖镇上出售农作物了
You won't be selling your produce in Banshee anymore.
你不能在任何地方出售农作物了
You won't be selling your produce anywhere.
凯
Kai!
为什么  凯  为什么
女妖镇正处于悲伤与危险之中
These are sad and dangerous times for the town of Banshee.
四位年轻女子
Four young women
遭到惨无人道的杀害
have been brutally and senselessly murdered
凶手是个内心扭曲的懦夫
by a twisted coward
专门残害弱小
who preys on those who're smaller and weaker than himself.
你是图科吗
You Tocho?
我能一起画吗
Can I draw, too?
女妖镇警局全体和联调局
My entire department along with the FBI
夜以继日
have been working around the clock to
希望找出并逮捕凶手
identify and apprehend this killer.
但凶手显然仍逍遥法外
But obviously we haven't yet.
我为此承担全部责任
And for that, I take full responsibility.
我以前当过警察
You know, I used to be a policeman.
虽然现在不已经不是了
Even though I don't do it anymore,
但有时候我还是会帮他们
sometimes I still help them
赶走坏人
chase the bad guys away.
我想在此立誓  向大家作出承诺
I would like to make a pledge, a promise,
女妖镇警长  布罗克·洛特斯
我会对此案追究到底  直到吉尔·弗兰西斯
that I will not stop until Jill Francis,
梅瑞迪斯·科布尔  阿曼达·克罗利
Meredith Coble, Amanda Crowley,
和丽贝卡·鲍曼
and Rebecca Bowman
讨回她们应得的公道
receive the justice they so desperately deserve.
这是那晚你在林子里见到的人吗
Is that the man you saw the other night in the woods?
看看你画的他头上的这些东西
See these things you drew on his head?
他戴帽子了吗
Was he wearing a hat?
是犄角吗
Are they horns?
现在...
And now...
我要直接与你对话
I would like to talk directly to you...
你这个可悲可怜的懦夫
you sad, pathetic coward.
我不明白你觉得自己是什么人
I don't know what you have convinced yourself that you are,
可你永远都只是个可悲的怪物
but you will never be anything more than a sad little freak.
我会找到你  一定会找到你
I am gonna find you. I am.
我会解决掉你  还要让你
And I'm gonna take you down and I'm gonna make sure
再也不能伤害任何人
that you never hurt anyone else ever again.
你喝什么
You drinking?
威士忌加冰
Whiskey, rocks.
我听人说这地方特别好
I've heard good things about this place.
但真正的料在哪呢
But where's the real action?
我不知道你到底在说什么
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
我想你知道
I think you do.
回家吧  小姑娘
Go home, little girl.
找到我想要的  我就回家
Not until I find what I'm looking for.
多谢你的小费
Thank you for the tip.
真是恶心
That's just nasty.
你他妈干什么
What the fuck?
你不该来进来
You shouldn't be here.
是吗  我总爱做不该做的事
Yeah? Well, bad choices are sort of my thing.
不过你肯定知道这点
But you must know something about that.
我不认识你
I don't know who you are,
可这里的规矩很简单
but the rules here are very simple.
进来了  就休想毫发无损的出去
No one walks out the same way they walk in.
是吗  那我还是免了吧
Yeah, I'm gonna pass on that.
我在性方面比较变态  可你们
See, I'm pretty kinky, but you guys,
变态至极了
you're fucked up.
你也来这儿啦
You come here, too?
你怎么知道我在这里
How'd you know I was here?
之前不知道
I didn't.
奇诺小娃画了这个
The Kinaho kid drew this.
镇上只有这地方有长角的怪物
This is the only place in town where the freaks have horns.
你怎么找到这里的
How'd you get here?
本案和联调局数据库里其他
Our murders are consistent with other ritualistic murders
祭祀谋杀手法一致
in the FBI database.
直指撒旦教
Pointed to Satanism.
蠢货  你这是在哪里做的
Hey, shitneck, where did you get your work done?
你这是在哪里做的
Where did you get your work done?
去你妈的
Get fucked.
回答错误
Wrong answer.
好好
Okay! Okay!
那人叫奎克  奎克医生
Guy named Quick. Dr. Quick.
-他是外科医生  -对  现在不是了
- He's a surgeon? - Yeah. No. He used to be.
他在哪里
Where do we find him?
在斯旺森一家干洗店后面工作
Works out of the back of a dry cleaner over on Swanson.
你们得培养新爱好了
You kids need to find a new hobby.
是你
It's you.
盖尔
Hey, Gail.
你好像很紧张
You seem nervous.
不  我只是...
No, I just--
只是没想到你来这里
I just didn't expect you to be here.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我没想吓到你
I didn't mean to startle you.
我一直在观察你  盖尔
I've been watching you, Gail.
你很安静
You're quiet,
不像其他某些信徒那么招摇
less flashy than some of the other acolytes.
但你的信念很纯粹
But your commitment is very pure.
我发现这点令人动心
I find that exciting.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们很像  盖尔
We're a lot alike, Gail.
你是真正的信徒  对吗
You're a true believer, aren't you?
对  我是
I am. I am.
那就好
That's good,
因为我选择给你
because I have chosen you
一项非常特别的荣誉
for a very special honor.
你愿与我共同侍奉他吗
Will you serve him with me?
我愿意  我愿意
I will. I will.
感谢你
Thank you.
有什么问题吗  副警长
Is there a problem, Deputy?
你报警说有小偷
Just answering your prowler call.
我们没报警
We didn't call no police.
那肯定是邻居报警了
Must have been your neighbors.
"肯定是"
Must have been.
当然了  但我们没邻居
'Course, we ain't got none of those.
没有  确实没有
No. No, you don't.
你怎么大老远把车停在路那头
Why'd you leave your car all the way at the end of the road?
到这边大门要走很远
It's a long walk to this here gate.
你住在这里吗
Do you live here?
只是过客
Just visiting.
这有很多监控设备
It's a lot of surveillance equipment.
你知道那句俗话
Well, you know what they say,
未雨绸缪
just 'cause you're paranoid
防范未然
don't mean they ain't all out to get you.
警世名言
Words to live by.
愿你今夜平安
Have a safe night.
我尽力
I'll do my best.
我就是想简单说几句
I just want to say a few things real quick.
感谢各位前来庆祝
I gotta thank you all for this celebration.
很高兴见到大家
It's great to see all of you.
我到周围转了转
Now, I look around and I see, man,
发现我走了后这里变化很大  很大
a lot of changes since I went in. A lot of changes.
可是吃了八年牢饭后
But after eight years in a cage,
只有一点未曾改变
there's one thing that hasn't changed at all.
那就是我对你们的承诺
That's my commitment to all of you.
不管怎样  你们这些混球是我的家人
Like it or not, you degenerates are my family.
家人就是不论发生什么
Family sticks together.
都要团结一致
No matter what.
而就我个人而言
And on a personal note,
我已刑满归来
I've done my time.
受到了惩罚
Paid my dues.
我已受够了以成大业之名
And I'm tired of living in the gutter
过着穷困潦倒的日子
in the name of the cause.
我们为了信仰牺牲了很多
We sacrifice a lot for our beliefs.
但我们也该享受一些战利品
But we's also allowed to enjoy some of the spoils of war.
所以我有个计划
So I have laid plans.
计划将一些战利品
Plans that will put some of those spoils
据为己有
into our own pockets.
有了钱就有了安全保障
And with that money comes security.
也就有了权利
And with that, power.
今晚我们共饮
Tonight we drink.
今夜我们共爽
Tonight we fuck.
而明天
And tomorrow,
将开启新的雅利安人革命
the new Aryan revolution begins.
刚刚是什么情况
What the fuck was that?
那是新的开始  加尔文
That was a new beginning,Calvin.
钱就是你笼络人心的手段吗
Money? That's fucking pitch?
兄弟会什么时候以金钱至上了
Money? Since when has the Brotherhood been about money?
别这么混蛋  卡尔文
Don't be a fuck up, Calvin.
我只关心我的想法  就付不了房租
I take care of my own ideas don't pay the rent.
我们不能都西装革履
We can't all put on ties,
去拍老板的马屁  求好处
suck dick for some shit asking glamour.
你是在卖兄弟会
You're selling out the Brotherhood,
出卖我们打回来的天下  你为此坐牢的一切
everything we worked for, look, you went to fucking jail for.
我坐牢是为了我的兄弟们  家人
I went to jail for my brothers, for my family,
还有你这个白眼狼
for you, you ungrateful shit.
出狱时  发现你他妈的抢了我的生意
And I come out and I see you shitting all over the deals I made,
还视我如眼中钉
looking at me like I'm in your fucking way.
玛吉嫁错兄弟了
Now, Maggie, she married the wrong brother.
柯特或许有点糊涂  但他至少比你有种
Kurt might be confused, but at least he got balls.
行
Okay.
派对开始
Let's fucking party!
邦克  不是吧
Bunker. Really?
你要干什么
What are you doing?
你别忘了你车上装着GPS跟踪器
You know you have a GPS tracker on your cruiser.
你他妈的要干什么
What the hell are you doing?
布罗克  你别管我
Brock, leave me alone.
这可是兰德尔·瓦茨  他们的头儿
That's Randall Watts, the top dog.
他刚出狱  一枪毙了他  就完事了
He just got out of jail. One shot in his head and this is over.
一枪就能把整个兄弟会招来
One shot and you're gonna have the entire Brotherhood up here.
给我起来  妈的  邦克  别犯傻
Get up. God damn it, Bunker. Be smart.
一定要比他们更有脑子
We've gotta be smarter than them.
我们要掌握主动权后
We cannot beat them at their game.
再以其人之道还治其人之身
We gotta beat them at ours.
你穿着制服  用局里的枪
You're in uniform using one of our vehicles.
你到底怎么想的
What the hell are you thinking?
-对不起  -别他妈道歉
- I'm sorry. - No, fuck sorry.
这个镇子彻底乱了
This town's going off the rails.
连环杀手伺机杀人
We got a serial killer on the prowl,
市长是黑道上的人
we got a mayor who's a gangster,
你还想挑衅新纳粹
and you want to start a war with the neo-Nazis.
看着我
Look at me.
现在能让我在乎的东西也不多了  邦克
I don't have much in my life that I care about anymore, Bunker.
我只想好好守护女妖镇
Just Banshee. That's it.
我要是就此束手就擒  就太不是人了
And I'll be damned if I'm gonna give up this town without a fight.
你现在就要做出选择
Now you gotta decide right now
你是想通过正当手段跟我并肩作战
whether you want to fight with me the right way
还是要给我捅一个更大的篓子
or you're just gonna be another headache I gotta handle.
好吧
Okay.
好什么
Okay?
我跟你
Okay.
我们快离开这儿
Let's get the hell out of here.
刚才那番话
That was a...
说得不错
good speech.
靠
Damn.
还真是挨了几拳
I took a couple shots back there.
你也没少打他们
But you gave some, too.
别担心
Hey, don't worry.
床底下我检查过了
I already checked under the bed.
你应该好好休息
You should get some rest.
没错
I should.
但我一个人喝不完一瓶威士忌
But I can't drink all this scotch by myself.
你的酒量  我们都很清楚
Yeah, I think we both know that's not true.
我可不信你目睹了那种场面
Try and tell me you don't need a drink
还不想来一杯压压惊
after that madness we just witnessed back there.
你说得有道理
Yeah, you have a point.
天呐
Jeez.
我们要追查那个外科医生吗
So, we gonna track down that surgeon?
我已经不是警察了
I'm not a cop anymore.
就算是以前
Even when I was,
我也比较喜欢一个人行动
I wasn't much of a team player.
是啊  我也是
Yeah, me neither.
但我们要调查同一个人
But we're both out there looking for the same guy.
一起行动也好有个照应
Might as well have each other's backs.
我知道你一个人也没问题
I know you can go it alone.
我也是  所以他们才会派我来
Me, too. That's why they sent me.
但这个人
But this guy is
不是一般的狠角色
a different kind of bad news.
而且你住在这里
And this is your town.
你了解这里的情况
You know the lay of the land.
而我很需要有人支援我
And I could really use the backup.
行吧
Okay.
玛吉
Maggie.
我找你好久了  他们把我爸放了
Oh, I've been trying to reach you. They let my dad out.
我知道  他之前找过我了
I know. He came to see me earlier.
你得想想办法啊  不能再等了
You've gotta do something, okay? You can't wait any longer.
我正处理了  玛吉  但这件事
I'm working on it, Maggie, but this is a lot bigger
不只牵连到你爸和加尔文
than just your father and Calvin.
你是说毒品吧
You're talking about the drugs.
你怎么知道的
How do you know about that?
我在加尔文桌上发现的
I found these on Calvin's desk.
天呐  玛吉  要是被他发现你...
Jesus Christ, Maggie, if he caught you...
我是想尽力帮你啊
I'm just trying to give you what you need, okay?
这好像是生产进度表
This is some kind of a production schedule.
我觉得可能要有笔大交易了
There's some big delivery coming up, I think.
这放在加尔文桌上
This was on Calvin's desk?
是啊  怎么了
Yeah, why?
这些量非常巨大
These are very large quantities.
不仅仅是本地毒品交易了
This isn't just local drug dealing.
这是
This is...
这些数字
These numbers...
我发誓  这一切就要结束了
I swear to you, this is almost over.
但你必须回家  装作什么事都没发生
But I need you to go home and pretend like everything's okay.
柯特  我不能再这样下去了好吗
Kurt, I can't do this much longer, okay?
我一直担惊受怕
I'm scared all the time.
我知道  我会救你出来的
I know. I will get you out of there.
我保证
I promise.
有给我倒一杯吗
So, did you make me one?
我想你离开这里
I want you out of here.
这是我家  我不欢迎你
This is my house and you are not welcome.
这么任性啊  加尔文
That's cute, Calvin, but...
现在翅膀才硬  好像有点晚了
it's a little late to grow a pair.
你能不能闭嘴  给我倒杯酒
How about you just shut the fuck up and pour me a drink?
算了  我自己来吧
Fuck it. I'll do it myself.